[laughter]
[music]
>> Hello.
>> Got it?
>> I'm Remo.
R E M O
>> Remo?
>> That's right, baby.
Hello.
Want a bet?
>> Huh?
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Hey, one more thing.
Break a leg. No worries. Bye.
>> I think he's left your laundry.
>> [laughter]
>> Hello.
Hello.
Oscar.
Boss.
Good. I have to do DNA test for him.
Okay.
Boss.
Sorry, sir.
>> [music]
>> Marry me now, jumbo.
I'm B.
>> Okay, switch on.
Sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you.
Morning, Mama.
>> [laughter]
>> You don't worry. I will help you.
Tell me, Mr. Ramanujan.
Are you feeling comfortable?
What's your problem?
Tension headache.
>> Tension either.
>> Mhm.
>> I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'll get upset. I'll get a headache.
I'll get a headache.
My head will feel like it's going to
explode.
>> What will happen then?
>> Suddenly everything will go blank.
I won't know what's happening. When I
open my eyes, I'll be somewhere else, in
a different
dress,
different manner.
>> What will happen after that? [laughter]
>> I don't know.
>> You will become something.
>> Ah.
>> You will see. Deep inside
>> like my head is going to explode.
>> Okay, okay, okay. After that, after
that, after that.
>> My whole body will
sweat and shiver.
>> Okay, okay. What will happen after that?
>> After that
I don't know.
>> Ambi, I know you can. Come on.
>> Think.
>> Think, think, think.
>> My head hurts.
>> After the pain, after the [groaning]
pain, after the pain.
>> No.
>> Hey, doctor.
Why are you torturing Ambi?
Anniyan.
Oh.
What is your relationship with
Ambi? Ambi is a worm.
A coward. A useless fellow.
Wherever injustice happens, he will talk
about rules, give complaints, file
cases, and cry and whine.
I couldn't stop his injustice. I
couldn't stop his injustice.
I decided to stop him.
How? I opened a website called
Anniyan.com.
I put up 15 cards asking people to
inform me about any injustice happening
anywhere.
It spread all over the country.
Complaints and information piled up on
the internet.
Now, all the injustices in the country
are in my database. What are you going
to do with them? I don't have to tell
you that. It's none of your business.
You doctor.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey doctor,
you crazy?
Ask me.
Rose means beauty.
Beauty means Nandy. As sweet as candy.
Dude, I'm Remo. Ramp walk model Rosella
gentle lover style.
Amby, gosh.
Amby's a useless fellow.
Now she loves me. You love a woman, just
tell her that she's the one. Da da da da
da da.
She needs somebody to tell her that it's
going to last.
SIMPLE.
IT'S ALL FOR LOVE. All for love.
You love a woman, tell her that she's
really wanted.
>> You got something?
Boss, very strange website, boss.
In fact, all these things are good
website, right?
No, boss.
You know, visual stuff
you don't know what I mean, right?
>> [laughter]
>> Garu the problem?
Exactly, sir.
It's very, very hot.
Good work,
another clue, huh?
I'm going to stop him right away, boss.
I just want to know what you want to do
with it.
I'll go find him.
I'll bring you my camera to the stadium,
boss.
I'm busy.
Hey, hey, watch it, buddy.
May
I'm Remo, the ramp model. I'm going
to kiss him goodbye for
What?
Why?
Hey, Nandy.
What?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, my glasses.
Oh.
What now?
Hey, hey, hey, Nandy.
Hey.
You
You mean Amby?
Yes.
What?
Huh?
>> What?
Nandini,
this is not fair.
You can't do this to me. I'm crazy about
you.
I'm hurting inside.
I can't take this.
This is killing me.
Nandini, are you
>> [crying]
[laughter]
>> I don't know about you, Ambi.
Huh?
Mhm. Huh?
Mhm.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know about you, Ambi.
>> I can't breathe.
>> I'm real.
>> Call the police.
>> Sir.
>> You want to search help me and confirm?
>> Huh?
>> Are you happy?
>> [music]
>> Sumby.
>> Do you think I'm a fool?
>> Know my job.
>> [music]
>> Ah!
>> [laughter]
>> Hey!
Come on, Natty.
No, I sent you a good idea.
>> [screaming]
>> Sir.
>> Hey!
>> [groaning]
[laughter]
>> Sir.
>> Hey!
Not a very good again.
You want to get your magic OUT OF MY
YOU CAN SEE HOW THE PARTY CAN SHOW YOU
HOW
>> [screaming]